question_data = [
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "English new wave musician Gary Numan founded the video game development company Facepunch Studios in March 2009.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The Mann Co. Store from Team Fortress 2 has the slogan &quot;We hire mercenaries and get in fights&quot;.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In Kingdom Hearts the Paopu fruit is said to intertwine the destinies for two people forever.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "The 2005 video game &quot;Call of Duty 2: Big Red One&quot; is not available on PC.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In Team Fortress 2, being disguised as a scout or medic results in a speed boost.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     },
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Splatoon, the Squid Sisters are named Tako and Yaki.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "In the game &quot;Subnautica&quot;, a &quot;Spadefish&quot; will attack you.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon Sun and Moon, a male Salandit can evolve to a Salazzle.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "In Terraria, you can craft the Cell Phone pre-hardmode.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the &quot;S.T.A.L.K.E.R.&quot; series, the Freedom faction wishes to destroy the supernatural area known as  &quot;the Zone&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
